{
    "subject": "resource/A_Million_Ways_to_Die_in_the_West",
    "predicate": "property/starring",
    "object": "resource/Charlize_Theron",
    "human_readable": "A Million Ways to Die in the West stars Charlize Theron.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9826871752738953,
            "question": "Is Charlize Theron in 'A Million Ways to Die in the West'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.929379403591156,
            "question": "Are there any other actors in 'A Million Ways to Die in the West' besides Charlize Theron?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9170024991035461,
            "question": "Who stars in the movie 'A Million Ways to Die in the West'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7816931009292603,
            "question": "Who directed 'A Million Ways to Die in the West'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7080332040786743,
            "question": "What genre is 'A Million Ways to Die in the West' likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6857880353927612,
            "question": "What year was 'A Million Ways to Die in the West' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37157317996025085,
            "question": "What roles has Charlize Theron played?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3550071716308594,
            "question": "What is the name of the movie starring Charlize Theron?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31577855348587036,
            "question": "What other movies has Charlize Theron been in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30096352100372314,
            "question": "Can you name a film featuring Charlize Theron?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=A Million Ways to Die in the West stars Charlize Theron.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7885_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What other movies has Charlize Theron been in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7885_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the movie starring Charlize Theron?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7885_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What roles has Charlize Theron played?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7885_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7885_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7885_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7885_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7885_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7885_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7885_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7885_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7885_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7885_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7885_60.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The text explicitly mentions that Charlize Theron stars in the movie \"A Million Ways to Die in the West\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Charlize Theron stars in \"A Million Ways to Die in the West,\" thus supporting the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}